作为一个应用开发者  我们有责任让自己的应用一旦被使用就深深吸引住用户
As app developers, it's our job to maintain the illusion that once started,
时刻在后台等待着用户的使用
every app is waiting patiently in the background looking for
所以  一旦用户再次把你的应用转回到前台
its chance to be the star when called on. So whenever the user switches back to
你必须要显示出跟离开时一样的UI界面
your app, whether or not the system is kilted in the interim,
无论它是否曾被系统终止过
they should be presented with the same UI they had when they left. To help,
为了帮助应用保存和恢复状态  Android系统提供了一对特殊的句柄
Android has a pair of handles specifically for persisting state in these
当你的应用进入不活跃状态  也就是暂停onPause状态时
circumstances. On save instance data is called immediately before on pause. So
保存实例数据函数会被立即调用
as soon as your app is no longer active, an on
如果你的应用被系统终止过
restore instance data is called immediately after on create, but
在重新创建时  恢复实例数据函数会被立即调用
only if the app is being restarted after having been terminated by the system.
这意味着你可以读取出上次退出时  也就是这里
That means you can read the bundle of state information saved the last time your
保存的那些状态信息
app was moved to the foreground here. The next time,
即使系统终止了你的程序  下次你也可以使用这些参数
you'll use the switches to your app even if it was killed by the system in
用这个Bundle里的数据  你可以重新恢复跟上次离开时一模一样的UI
the mean time. Using that bundle you can return your ui to the same state it
这提供了一种不间断的效果
was the last time the user saw it creating a seamless transition that hides
并把资源管理的操作掩盖在后台  不为用户所见  原因就是这些了
the resource management happening under the covers. That's enough of the why,
让Dan给大家介绍一下如何把这些理论与实际结合起来
let's go back to Dan and see how to put this theory into practice.